[
  {
      "product_id": 1,
      "licence_name": "POKEMON",
      "category_name": "Figuras coleccionables",
      "product_name": "PIDGEOTTO",
      "product_description": "Figura coleccionable pokemon",
      "product_price": 1799.99,
      "dues": 10,
      "stock": 5,
      "product_sku": "PKM001001",
      "img_front": "/img/pokemon/pidgeotto-1.webp",
      "img_back": "/img/pokemon/pidgeotto-box.webp"
  },
  {
      "product_id": 2,
      "licence_name": "HARRY POTTER",
      "category_name": "Figuras coleccionables",
      "product_name": "LUNA LOVEGOOD LION MASK",
      "product_description": "Figura coleccionable de Luna Lovegood - Saga Harry Pooter",
      "product_price": 1599.99,
      "dues": 10,
      "stock": 5,
      "product_sku": "HRP001001",
      "img_front": "/img/harry-potter/luna-1.webp",
      "img_back": "/img/harry-potter/luna-box.webp"
  },
  {
      "product_id": 3,
      "licence_name": "HARRY POTTER",
      "category_name": "Figuras coleccionables",
      "product_name": "HARRY POTTER",
      "product_description": "Figura coleccionable de Luna Lovegood - Saga Harry Pooter",
      "product_price": 1599.99,
      "dues": 10,
      "stock": 5,
      "product_sku": "HRP001002",
      "img_front": "/img/harry-potter/harry-1.webp",
      "img_back": "/img/harry-potter/harry-box.webp"
  },
  {
      "product_id": 4,
      "licence_name": "HARRY POTTER",
      "category_name": "Figuras coleccionables",
      "product_name": "HERMAIONE GRANGER",
      "product_description": "Figura coleccionable de Luna Lovegood - Saga Harry Pooter",
      "product_price": 1599.99,
      "dues": 10,
      "stock": 5,
      "product_sku": "HRP001003",
      "img_front": "/img/harry-potter/hermione-1.webp",
      "img_back": "/img/harry-potter/hermione-box.webp"
  },
  {
      "product_id": 5,
      "licence_name": "HARRY POTTER",
      "category_name": "Figuras coleccionables",
      "product_name": "SNAPE PATRONUS",
      "product_description": "Figura coleccionable de Luna Lovegood - Saga Harry Pooter",
      "product_price": 1599.99,
      "dues": 10,
      "stock": 5,
      "product_sku": "HRP001004",
      "img_front": "/img/harry-potter/snape-patronus-1.webp",
      "img_back": "/img/harry-potter/snape-patronus-box.webp"
  },
  {
      "product_id": 6,
      "licence_name": "STAR WARS",
      "category_name": "Figuras coleccionables",
      "product_name": "STORMTROOPER LIGHTSABER",
      "product_description": "Figura coleccionable Stormtrooper Lightsaber",
      "product_price": 1899.99,
      "dues": 10,
      "stock": 5,
      "product_sku": "STW001001",
      "img_front": "/img/star-wars/trooper-1.webp",
      "img_back": "/img/star-wars/trooper-box.webp"
  },
  {
      "product_id": 7,
      "licence_name": "POKEMON",
      "category_name": "Figuras coleccionables",
      "product_name": "CHARMANDER",
      "product_description": "Figura coleccionable pokemon",
      "product_price": 1799.99,
      "dues": 10,
      "stock": 5,
      "product_sku": "PKM001002",
      "img_front": "/img/pokemon/charmander-1.webp",
      "img_back": "/img/pokemon/charmander-box.webp"
  },
      {
          "product_id": 8,
          "licence_name": "POKEMON",
          "category_name": "Figuras coleccionables",
          "product_name": "DRAGONITE",
          "product_description": "Figura coleccionable pokemon",
          "product_price": 1799.99,
          "dues": 10,
          "stock": 5,
          "product_sku": "PKM001003",
          "img_front": "/img/pokemon/dragonite-1.webp",
          "img_back": "/img/pokemon/dragonite-box.webp"
      },
      {
          "product_id": 9,
          "licence_name": "POKEMON",
          "category_name": "Figuras coleccionables",
          "product_name": "PIKACHU",
          "product_description": "Figura coleccionable pokemon",
          "product_price": 1799.99,
          "dues": 10,
          "stock": 5,
          "product_sku": "PKM001004",
          "img_front": "/img/pokemon/pikachu-1.webp",
          "img_back": "/img/pokemon/pikachu-box.webp"
      },
      {
          "product_id": 10,
          "licence_name": "POKEMON",
          "category_name": "Figuras coleccionables",
          "product_name": "VULPIX",
          "product_description": "Figura coleccionable pokemon",
          "product_price": 1799.99,
          "dues": 10,
          "stock": 5,
          "product_sku": "PKM001004",
          "img_front": "/img/pokemon/vulpix-1.webp",
          "img_back": "/img/pokemon/vulpix-box.webp"
      },

  {
      "product_id": 11,
      "licence_name": "STAR WARS",
      "category_name": "Figuras coleccionables",
      "product_name": "BABY YODA",
      "product_description": "Figura coleccionable Baby Yoda - Saga Star Wars & The Mandalorian",
      "product_price": 1899.99,
      "dues": 10,
      "stock": 5,
      "product_sku": "STW001002",
      "img_front": "/img/star-wars/baby-yoda-1.webp",
      "img_back": "/img/star-wars/baby-yoda-box.webp"
  },
  {
      "product_id": 12,
      "licence_name": "STAR WARS & THE MANDALORIAN",
      "category_name": "Figuras coleccionables",
      "product_name": "BOBBA FETT",
      "product_description": "Figura coleccionable Bobba Fett - Saga Star Wars & The Mandalorian",
      "product_price": "$1799,99",
      "dues": 10,
      "stock": 5,
      "product_sku": "STW001003",
      "img_front": "/img/star-wars/bobbafeth-1.webp",
      "img_back": "/img/star-wars/bobbafeth-box.webp"
  },
  {
      "product_id": 13,
      "licence_name": "STAR WARS & THE MANDALORIAN",
      "category_name": "Figuras coleccionables",
      "product_name": "LUKE SKYWALKER",
      "product_description": "Figura coleccionable  Luke Skywalker - Saga Star Wars & The Mandalorian",
      "product_price": "$1799,99",
      "dues": 10,
      "stock": 5,
      "product_sku": "STW001004",
      "img_front": "/img/star-wars/luke-1.webp",
      "img_back": "/img/star-wars/luke-box.webp"
  }
]